ICICI Lombard earns profit of ₹5577 crore,
declares dividend of ₹12.5 per share ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company's profit has declined by ₹2.2 per share
in the July-September quarter of the current financial year as
compared to ₹77.30 per share in the September quarter.
ICICI Lombard had earned a
profit of ₹90.5 crore in the July-September quarter of last year.
ICICI Lombard shares closed at ₹
8.25 on Wednesday, down ₹1.55 crore.
Gross direct premium income stood at ₹686 crore.
Gross direct premium income of ICICI Lombard
stood at ₹86 crore in the September quarter of the current financial year. During the same period last year, the
company's gross direct
premium income
was ₹5185 crore. This growth is much
higher than the industry growth of ₹12.5 per share. The
Board of Directors of ICICI Lombard
declared an interim dividend of ₹12.5 per share for the first half of the current financial year.  PBT in the first half
was Rs 1244 crore. In the first half of the current financial year,
ICICI Lombard's
PBT was Rs
84 crore. The
company's PBT has increased by 19.4 crore compared to the same period last year.
In the first half of last year,
ICICI Lombard's PBT was Rs 1075 crore.
In the second quarter of the current financial year, the
company's combined ratio is 103.9,
which was 105.1 in the second quarter of last year.
In the first half of the current financial year, the company's return on average
equity is 18, which
was 19.9 in the same period last year.